Tisch Library Records UA137
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Committee Files, 1908 -- 2006; 1965 -- 1995; UA137.004; 6.5 Linear Feet
  - Library Committee, 1986 -- 1989; UA137.004.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Library Council Meeting, 1956 -- 1965; UA137.004.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Library Council Meetings, 1965 -- 1968; UA137.004.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Library Council Meetings, 1968 -- 1971; UA137.004.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Library Council Meetings, 1972 -- 1974; UA137.004.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Library Council Meetings, 1975 -- 1977; UA137.004.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Library Council Meetings, 1977 -- 1981; UA137.004.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Library Council Meetings, 1982 -- 1985; UA137.004.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Library Council Notes Index, 1956 -- 1971; UA137.004.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Personnel Committee, 1968 -- 1973; UA137.004.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Professional Staff Meetings, 1959 -- 1980; UA137.004.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Reference Services Meetings, 1984 -- 1986; UA137.004.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Staff Development Travel Committee, 1992 -- 1993; UA137.004.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Staff Recognition Award Committee, 1992; UA137.004.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Student Library Committee, 1955 -- 1970; UA137.004.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Unit Heads Meetings, 1985; UA137.004.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Unit Heads Meetings, 1989; UA137.004.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - University-wide Advisory Committee on Libraries, 1962; UA137.004.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - University-wide Advisory Committee on Libraries, 1963 -- 1979; UA137.004.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - University Library Council, 1984; UA137.004.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Library Assembly: Berger Revision and Evaluation, 2000 -- 2001; UA137.004.012.00026; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - University Library Council, 1985; UA137.004.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - University Library Council, 1986; UA137.004.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - University Library Council, 1987; UA137.004.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - University Library Council, 1988; UA137.004.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Visiting Committee, 1967 -- 1976; UA137.004.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Visiting Committee, 1985 -- 1986; UA137.004.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Visiting Committee, Correspondence, 1971 -- 1981; UA137.004.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Visiting Committee Meetings, 1959 -- 1978; UA137.004.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Visiting Committee Membership, 1971 -- 1976; UA137.004.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Wessell Advisory Council, 1990 -- 1993; UA137.004.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Wessell Advisory Council, 1993 -- 1995; UA137.004.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Wessell Department Heads Meetings, 1984 -- 1985; UA137.004.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Wessell Department Heads Meetings, 1986; UA137.004.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Wessell Department Heads Meetings, 1987 -- 1988; UA137.004.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Wessell Department Heads Meetings, 1989 -- 1990; UA137.004.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Tisch Advisory Council: Web @ Tisch, 1999 -- 2000; UA137.004.013.00016; Rogan, Michael (Box 13)
  - Tisch Advisory Council: Systems - Memos, 1993 -- 2001; UA137.004.013.00017; Rogan, Michael (Box 13)
  - Tisch Advisory Council: Staff Development Committee, 1997 -- 1999; UA137.004.013.00018; Rogan, Michael (Box 13)
  - Tisch Advisory Council: Misc. Library Reports, 1990 -- 1991; UA137.004.013.00019; Rogan, Michael (Box 13)
  - Tisch Advisory Council: BLC Library Catalog, 2000 -- 2002; UA137.004.013.00020; Rogan, Michael (Box 13)
  - Tisch Advisory Council: ULC, 1999 -- 2002; UA137.004.013.00021; Rogan, Michael (Box 13)
  - Tisch Advisory Council: ULC Staff Development Team, 1999 -- 2001; UA137.004.013.00022; Rogan, Michael (Box 13)
  - Tisch Advisory Council: Adhoc Committee on Searches, 1999 -- 2001; UA137.004.013.00023; Rogan, Michael (Box 13)
  - Data Assessment Team: Tisch Library Survey, 2001; UA137.004.014.00001; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Data Assessment Team: Tisch Library Survey, 2000; UA137.004.014.00002; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Data Assessment Team: Tisch Library Survey, 1999; UA137.004.014.00003; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Data Assessment Team: Arts and Sciences Library User Survey, 1994 -- 1995; UA137.004.014.00004; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Data Assessment Team: Tisch Survey, 2004; UA137.004.014.00005; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Data Assessment Team: Senior Survey, 2004; UA137.004.014.00006; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Data Assessment Team: DAT, 2004; UA137.004.014.00007; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Data Assessment Team: DAT, 2001 -- 2003; UA137.004.014.00008; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Not Associated w/ Any Team: All Staff Meetings, 2002 -- 2003; UA137.004.014.00009; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Not Associated w/ Any Team: Archives and Special Collections, 1994 -- 1997; UA137.004.014.00010; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Not Associated w/ Any Team: Audio Lab Archives, 1990; UA137.004.014.00011; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Music Cataloging Outsourcing Team: Flourish - Music Contract Cataloging, 1998; UA137.004.014.00012; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Strategic Planning Team: Strategic Plan, 1999 -- 2000; UA137.004.014.00013; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Strategic Planning Team: Strategic Plan - Task Force A, 1999; UA137.004.014.00014; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Strategic Planning Team: Strategic Plan - Task Force B, 1999 -- 2000; UA137.004.014.00015; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Strategic Planning Team: Strategic Plan - Task Force C, 1999; UA137.004.014.00016; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Strategic Planning Team: Strategic Plan - Task Force D, 1999; UA137.004.014.00017; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Strategic Planning Team: Strategic Plan - Task Force E, 1999; UA137.004.014.00018; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - User Services Team: User Service Heads FY04 FY05, 2004 -- 2005; UA137.004.014.00019; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - User Services Team: User Services Heads FY99-FY03, 1999 -- 2003; UA137.004.014.00020; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - User Services Team: BLC Output Measurer - Workshop, 2003; UA137.004.014.00021; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - ILS Implementation: Lending Team, 1992 -- 2004; UA137.004.014.00022; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - ILS Implementation: Documentation, Tables, Questions + Millenium Authorizations, 2002 -- 2004; UA137.004.014.00023; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - ILS Implementation: Agendas + Minutes, 2003 -- 2005; UA137.004.014.00024; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - ILS Implementation: Cataloging + Indexing Task Force, 2003 -- 2004; UA137.004.014.00025; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Librarians Assembly, 1998 -- 2003; UA137.004.014.00027; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council: Disaster Plan, 1994; UA137.004.014.00028; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council: Tufts University Self Study Report to the New England Association of Schools and Colleges, 2003; UA137.004.014.00029; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council: Collection Budget - FY99, 1999; UA137.004.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council: Collection Budget - FY98, 1998; UA137.004.014.00031; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council: Collection Budget - FY97, 1997; UA137.004.014.00032; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council: Collection Budget - FY96, 1996; UA137.004.014.00033; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council: Collection Budget - FY95, 1995; UA137.004.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council: Old Collection Development - Policies, 1992 -- 1995; UA137.004.014.00035; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council (Feb. 1999-FY00-FY01-FY02) [part 1], 1999 -- 2002; UA137.004.014.00036; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council (Feb. 1999-FY00-FY01-FY02) [part 2], 1999 -- 2002; UA137.004.014.00037; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council, 2002 -- 2003; UA137.004.014.00038; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Collection Development Council, 2004 -- 2005; UA137.004.014.00039; Rogan, Michael (Box 14)
  - Berger Technology Transfer Grants, 2001 -- 2006; UA137.004.014.00040 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Advisory Council FY00, 1999 -- 2000; UA137.004.015.00001; Rogan, Michael (Box 15)
  - Advisory Council FY01, 2000 -- 2001; UA137.004.015.00002; Rogan, Michael (Box 15)
  - Advisory Council FY02, 2001 -- 2002; UA137.004.015.00003; Rogan, Michael (Box 15)
  - Advisory Council FY03, 2002 -- 2003; UA137.004.015.00004; Rogan, Michael (Box 15)
  - Advisory Council FY04, 2003 -- 2004; UA137.004.015.00005; Rogan, Michael (Box 15)
  - Advisory Council FY05, 2004 -- 2005; UA137.004.015.00006; Rogan, Michael (Box 15)
- Buildings and Plans, 1940 -- 2009; 1960 -- 1990; UA137.005; 3.65 Linear Feet; 90 Digital Object(s) Of the 90 digital objects, one digital object comprises 59 files.; 91 Megabytes
  This series contains materials related to the facilities serving Tisch Library, its predecessors, and other libraries at Tufts. Most notably, there is considerable information regarding the Health Sciences Library facilities.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Building Expansion, 1985 -- 1987; UA137.005.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Building Program Committee, 1987; UA137.005.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Campbell and Aldrich architects, 1960 -- 1962; UA137.005.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - Chemistry Library facilities, 1971; UA137.005.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Eaton Library, Gott Memorial, 1940 -- 1950; UA137.005.015.00011 (Box 15)
    Includes list of contributors to the Charles Gott Memorial Fund, December 7, 1950.
  - Engineering and Science Library facilities, 1978; UA137.005.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Fletcher School, brief to the the architect, 1976; UA137.005.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Fletcher School library, 1978 -- 1979; UA137.005.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - HEFA Grant proposal, 1964; UA137.005.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, correspondence, 1901 -- 1982; UA137.005.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, correspondence, 1908 -- 1982; UA137.005.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, correspondence, 1983; UA137.005.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, Executive Committee, 1983; UA137.005.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, Executive Committee, 1983; UA137.005.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, facilities, 1982; UA137.005.015.00021a (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, Educational Resources Committee, 1982; UA137.005.015.00021b (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, facilities, 1983 -- 1985; UA137.005.015.00021c (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, planning, 1982; UA137.005.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, reports, 1982; UA137.005.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Health Sciences Education Building, Steering Committee, 1981 -- 1983; UA137.005.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, 1982; UA137.005.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, 1983; UA137.005.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, background documents, 1977 -- 1980; UA137.005.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, design, 1978; UA137.005.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, planning, 1969 -- 1972; UA137.005.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, planning, 1977; UA137.005.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, planning, 1978; UA137.005.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, planning, 1980 -- 1981; UA137.005.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, planning, nutrition, 1978; UA137.005.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - Health Sciences Library, planning, Veterinary Medicine, 1976 -- 1979; UA137.005.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - LAN and PCs, 1987 -- 1988; UA137.005.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Library Facilities Committee, 1974; UA137.005.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Library Facilities Committee, 1975; UA137.005.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - Library Pamphlets, 1979 -- 1996; UA137.005.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Lilly Music Library construction records, 1998 -- 2009; UA137.001039; 91 Megabytes; 90 Digital Object(s)
    - Meeting and planning documents, 1998 October -- 2009 December; UA137.001040; 57.8 Megabytes; 16 Digital Object(s)
      - Ideal attributes of new music library, 1998 October 29; UA137.001041; 10.6 Kilobytes
      - Program revisions for the music library, 1999 May 03; UA137.001042; 39.5 Kilobytes
      - Michael Rogan design comments, 1999 June 21; UA137.001043; 42 Kilobytes
      - New music library design issues and concerns, 1999 June 29; UA137.001044; 52 Kilobytes
      - New library planned blurb 1, 1999 August 20; UA137.001045; 21 Kilobytes
      - Foundations that may be interested in music libraries, 1999 October 13; UA137.001046; 24.5 Kilobytes
      - New library planned blurb 2, 1999 December 20; UA137.001047; 22.5 Kilobytes
      - Indiana University Music Library thank you letter, 2000 March 03; UA137.001048; 28.5 Kilobytes
      - Program outline with square footages, 2000 March 30; UA137.001049; 59.5 Kilobytes
      - Request for shelving suggestions sent to Richard Tucker, 2000 April 03; UA137.001050; 29 Kilobytes
      - Music Library manifesto, 2000 June 01; UA137.001051; 20.5 Kilobytes
      - Library linear footage memo, 2000 June 06; UA137.001052; 64 Kilobytes
      - Design development kick off meeting, 2000 June 19; UA137.001053; 33.5 Kilobytes
      - Meeting notes, 2000 June 19; UA137.001054; 26 Kilobytes
      - Meeting notes, user group 1, 2000 June 19; UA137.001055; 25 Kilobytes
      - Meeting notes, 2000 July 18; UA137.001056; 25.5 Kilobytes
      - Meeting and planning documents, 2000 September -- 2009 December; UA137.001057; 57.3 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 59 files.
    - Music library and Granoff floor plans, circa 1999 August -- 2015 December; UA137.001058; 5.4 Megabytes; 18 Digital Object(s)
      - Old draft of first floor, 1999 August 31; UA137.001059; 534.2 Kilobytes
      - Third floor plan, 2000 August 22; UA137.001060; 110.8 Kilobytes
      - Granoff lower level floor plan, 2004 November 03; UA137.001061; 554.6 Kilobytes
      - Granoff upper level floor plan, 2004 November 03; UA137.001062; 540.7 Kilobytes
      - Perkins and Will draft floor plan, 2005 July 22; UA137.001063; 186.4 Kilobytes
      - Perkins and Will draft floor plan, 2005 July 22; UA137.001064; 368.8 Kilobytes
      - Perkins and Will draft floor plan, 2005 July 22; UA137.001065; 171.4 Kilobytes
      - Perkins and Will draft floor plan, 2005 July 22; UA137.001066; 201.5 Kilobytes
      - Granoff lower level east floor plan, circa 2007; UA137.001067; 368.8 Kilobytes
      - Granoff lower level west floor plan, circa 2007; UA137.001068; 186.4 Kilobytes
      - Granoff main level floor plan, circa 2007; UA137.001069; 171.4 Kilobytes
      - Granoff upper level floor plan, circa 2007; UA137.001070; 201.5 Kilobytes
      - Lilly Library detailed floor plan, circa 2008; UA137.001071; 405.4 Kilobytes
      - Lilly Music Library floor plan, 2008 March 17; UA137.001072; 185.5 Kilobytes
      - Lilly Music Library floor plan, 2008 March 17; UA137.001073; 216 Kilobytes
      - Lilly Library detailed floor plan, circa 2011; UA137.001074; 912 Kilobytes
      - Floor plan showing emergency egress, circa 2012; UA137.001075; 149.5 Kilobytes
      - Granoff basement floor plan, 2015 December 22; UA137.001076; 102.4 Kilobytes
    - Granoff construction photographs, 1999 -- 2005 September; UA137.001077; 21.7 Megabytes; 50 Digital Object(s)
      - David Perry architectual rendering, 1999; UA137.001078; 735 Kilobytes
      - Control room, 2004 November 15; UA137.001079; 96.4 Kilobytes
      - Architectural drawing of back left of Tufts music building, 2004 December 14; UA137.001080; 2.4 Megabytes
      - Architectural drawing of back right of Tufts music building, 2004 December 14; UA137.001081; 2.5 Megabytes
      - Construction site, 2005 June; UA137.001082; 498.4 Kilobytes
      - Construction site with Aidekman facade finishes, 2005 June; UA137.001083; 379.5 Kilobytes
      - Backhoe on mountain of dirt, 2005 July; UA137.001084; 488.2 Kilobytes
      - Construction site, 2005 July; UA137.001085; 487.4 Kilobytes
      - Backhoe digging hole, 2005 July; UA137.001086; 119.6 Kilobytes
      - Foundation wall, 2005 July; UA137.001087; 486.1 Kilobytes
      - Foundation wall, 2005 July; UA137.001088; 473.5 Kilobytes
      - Man in the hole dug for the foundation, 2005 July; UA137.001089; 483.6 Kilobytes
      - Hole dug for the foundation, 2005 July; UA137.001090; 483 Kilobytes
      - View of construction site, lower campus road, and track, 2005 July; UA137.001091; 480.7 Kilobytes
      - Pile of dirt and construction office trailers, 2005 July; UA137.001092; 487.9 Kilobytes
      - Pouring concrete foundation, 2005 July; UA137.001093; 485.4 Kilobytes
      - Pouring concrete foundation wall, 2005 July; UA137.001094; 482 Kilobytes
      - Preparing for foundation, 2005 July; UA137.001095; 484.6 Kilobytes
      - Construction site in need of draining after rain, 2005 July; UA137.001096; 480.2 Kilobytes
      - Soil stapling, 2005 July; UA137.001097; 471.5 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001098; 60.5 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001099; 61.2 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001100; 60.2 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001101; 60.5 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001102; 60.5 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001103; 60.3 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001104; 61.4 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001105; 60.8 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001106; 321.9 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 August; UA137.001107; 319.8 Kilobytes
      - Inside the future music library, 2005 August; UA137.001108; 170.4 Kilobytes
      - Pouring concrete foundation wall, 2005 August; UA137.001109; 59.9 Kilobytes
      - Rebar foundation perimeter for library wing, 2005 August; UA137.001110; 60.5 Kilobytes
      - West foundation wall for recital hall, 2005 August; UA137.001111; 59.7 Kilobytes
      - Music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001112; 492.2 Kilobytes
      - Music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001113; 491 Kilobytes
      - Music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001114; 498.3 Kilobytes
      - Music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001115; 481.8 Kilobytes
      - Music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001116; 475.2 Kilobytes
      - Music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001117; 485.5 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001118; 492.4 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001119; 471.7 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001120; 481.9 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001121; 476.1 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001122; 438.9 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001123; 458.7 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001124; 469 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001125; 499.5 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001126; 489.1 Kilobytes
      - New music building construction, 2005 September; UA137.001127; 478.7 Kilobytes
    - Library construction photographs, 2006 -- 2007; UA137.001128; 6.1 Megabytes; 6 Digital Object(s)
      - Library service desk, 2006; UA137.001129; 1.1 Megabytes
      - Listening stations and study carrels, 2006; UA137.001130; 1.1 Megabytes
      - Michael Rogan posing with library plans, 2006; UA137.001131; 3.1 Megabytes
      - Michael Rogan posing with library plans, 2006; UA137.001132; 210.5 Kilobytes
      - Music library office construction, 2006; UA137.001133; 471.5 Kilobytes
      - Collections room, 2007; UA137.001134; 193.8 Kilobytes
  - Lufkin - Math/Physics Library merger, 1968 -- 1978; UA137.005.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Lufkin Library, 1978; UA137.005.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - Medical-Dental Library, proposed modifications, 1976; UA137.005.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - Music Library facilities report, 1968 -- 1981; UA137.005.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - National Library of Medicine grant proposal, 1979; UA137.005.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - National Library of Medicine grant proposal materials, 1978; UA137.005.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - Nutrition, Occupational Therapy, and Veterinary Medicine, 1981; UA137.005.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - Photographs of architectural model, 1980 -- 1985; UA137.005.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - Report on a new engineering library, 1981; UA137.005.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - Reports on a new library, 1981 -- 1988; UA137.005.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Shelving, 1956; UA137.005.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Space Planning, 1978; UA137.005.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Space Planning, 1982 -- 1983; UA137.005.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Space Planning, 1984 -- 1985; UA137.005.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Space Planning, 1986 -- 1987; UA137.005.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Space Planning, Medical and Dental, 1974; UA137.005.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - Space Planning, survey, 1970 -- 1990; UA137.005.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Space Program for the University Library, 1987; UA137.005.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - Sysdac Circulation System, 1976; UA137.005.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - Tattle-tape book detection system, 1970 -- 1977; UA137.005.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Tisch Family Library, drawings and specs, 1993; UA137.005.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Tisch Library, 1994; UA137.005.017.00013 (Box 17)
    Groundbreaking ceremony invitation.
  - War Memorial Library, 1945 -- 1952; UA137.005.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, 1989 -- 1993; UA137.005.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, awards and publicity, 1965 -- 1966; UA137.005.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, A/V area renovation, 1988; UA137.005.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, archives construction, 1988; UA137.005.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, automation, 1982 -- 1984; UA137.005.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, Campbell and Aldrich architects, 1963; UA137.005.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, correspondence with Keyes Metcalf, 1963; UA137.005.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, descriptions, 1961 -- 1981; UA137.005.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, extension plans, 1987; UA137.005.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, floor plans, 1986 -- 1988; UA137.005.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, fire protection, 1988; UA137.005.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, furnishings, 1966; UA137.005.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, furnishings planning, 1964 -- 1968; UA137.005.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, government publications renovation, 1987; UA137.005.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, Komidar's correspondence, 1956 -- 1977; UA137.005.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, Komidar's correspondence, 1980 -- 1981; UA137.005.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - Wessell Library, Komidar's planning documents, 1959 -- 1979; UA137.005.018.00001 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, layout planning, 1963 -- 1964; UA137.005.018.00002 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, microforms renovation, 1988; UA137.005.018.00003 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, photographs, 1963 -- 1966; UA137.005.018.00004 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, reference area renovation, 1987; UA137.005.018.00005 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, renovations, 1988; UA137.005.018.00006 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, roof repairs, 1988; UA137.005.018.00007 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, seating, 1978 -- 1983; UA137.005.018.00008 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, space planning, 1963 -- 1964; UA137.005.018.00009 (Box UA137 Shared 3)